{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In what children's game are participants chased by someone designated \"It\"?",
      "content": ["Tag", "Simon Says", "Charades", "Hopscotch"],
      "correct": 0,
      "price": 500
    },
    {
      "question": "On a radio, stations are changed by using what control?",
      "content": ["Tuning", "Volume", "Bass", "Treble"],
      "correct": 0,
      "price": 1000
    },
    {
      "question": "A college graduate who receives a B.S. degree holds what official title?",
      "content": [
        "Bachelor of science",
        "Business scholar",
        "Baccalaureate staff",
        "Brainy student"
      ],
      "correct": 0,
      "price": 2000
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following telephone area codes is not a toll-free call in the United States?",
      "content": ["800", "828", "877", "888"],
      "correct": 1,
      "price": 4000
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the human body does glaucoma directly affect?",
      "content": ["Ear", "Nose", "Throat", "Eye"],
      "correct": 3,
      "price": 8000
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Tom Cruise's character in the \"Mission: Impossible\" movies?",
      "content": [
        "Frank Mackey",
        "Mitch McDeere",
        "Joel Goodson",
        "Ethan Hunt"
      ],
      "correct": 3,
      "price": 16000
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these materials is used to make vests bulletproof?",
      "content": ["Kevlar", "Lycra", "Gore-tex", "Polystyrene"],
      "correct": 0,
      "price": 32000
    },
    {
      "question": "What animal's name means \"river horse\" in Greek?",
      "content": ["Platypus", "Hippopotamus", "Rhinoceros", "Manatee"],
      "correct": 1,
      "price": 64000
    },
    {
      "question": "To take advantage of the earth's rotation, NASA launches most of its rockets in what direction?",
      "content": ["North", "East", "South", "West"],
      "correct": 1,
      "price": 125000
    },
    {
      "question": "College football's Independence Bowl is played in what city?",
      "content": ["Philadelphia", "Memphis", "Shreveport", "Tucson"],
      "correct": 2,
      "price": 250000
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these best describes music that is played \"pianissimo\"?",
      "content": ["Very soft", "Very fast", "Moderately loud", "Loud"],
      "correct": 0,
      "price": 500000
    },
    {
      "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the relationship between Oedipus and Antigone?",
      "content": [
        "Husband and wife",
        "Mentor and student",
        "Father and daughter",
        "Mother and son"
      ],
      "correct": 2,
      "price": 1000000
    }
  ]
}
